interactmedia.com.au 2009-12-18

# Legals || NetRegistry || Privacy Policy

Netregistry respects the Guidelines suggested by the [Australian Direct Marketing Association](http://www.adma.com.au/), in it's Code of Practice for Consumer Protection in ecommerce.

We also abide by the World Wide Web Consortium (W3C) Platform for Privacy Preferences Project (P3P). This policy is emerging as an industry standard providing a simple, automated way for users to gain more control over the use of personal information on web sites they visit.

In line with those guidelines, Netregistry would like you to be aware of the information we collect to provide your service. **We do not provide third parties with access to your personal data** , with the obvious exception of third party business partners such as the Domain Name Registries.

##  Information collected by Netregistry

Your contact information, including named individuals for administration, technical and billing issues. This information may include telephone, fax numbers and email addresses

Information about what services you have ordered from Netregistry:

  * Information about what services you have enquired
  * Your interest in receiving Netregistry email newsletters
  * Correspondance between you and Netregistry
  * A contact management system in which details of conversations might be written by employees
  * Encrypted credit card details
  * Your interaction with our websites

## What Netregistry does with your information

  * We do not make your personal information available to third parties, with the obvious exception of third party business partners such as the domain name registries that need to record your details when you register a domain name.
  * We do provide aggregate data to third parties (e.g. "we have 200,000 clients who are SMEs")
  * We will contact relevant people to communicate billing and technical issues
  * We store website data and email queued on our servers, only for use as back-up data should it be required
  * We may customise our email newsletters and communications to reflect your interest in a particular service
  * We access historic correspondance and details about earlier conversions in response to customer service issues and, to conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Netregistry
  * We store encryted credit card details to allow us to process the subscriptions to our services
  * We monitor and store your online requests for webpages and services for research and to keep a history of your transactions with the business (this might include recording the fact you set up and deleted an email account, or took a trial in one of our services, etc)

## Email communications

As a customer of Netregistry you will receive occasional email communications from Netregistry that relate to the services we provide to you, and you will have the option to opt-out of all non-essential email and postal mail.

If you have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us.
